Hi, in this video, I want to show you how to get a certificate when you complete the course.
I will show you example on the other course.
So, if you see after you complete all the course, you have a champion icon in the top
of the manual and you can, if you click on get certificate, you have a button and you
click on it.
On this page, you can see on the left side, the preview of your certificate that you will
successfully finish the course.
On the right side, you can download it as an image or PDF document or you can also share it
in social media's Facebook, LinkedIn or others.
Thank you to be a student on this course and especially for completion it.
I'm really happy to be your instructor, see ya!